Alright. So I'm gonna make a motion to come out of the executive session at 09:06PM
to resume our regularly scheduled meeting.
Do we have anyone that we need to invite back in?
No? Motion to adjourn.
Public speak will be
Oh, darn it. There's no public speak?
Okay. So there's no one left on our meeting. So There's nobody in the waiting room? Let me just check here. Nothing popped up. Hang on.
Nope. Nobody's in the waiting room. Okay. So The kebler elves waiting with cookie recipes. Should we wait for a couple minutes?
No. Okay. Who's making a motion to adjourn?
I already made one. You did. Motion to adjourn. I second. Scott seconded and all those in favor? All those in favor of cookies. Yay. Good night.
Good night. See
you guys.